https://www.tranceaddict.com/privacy.shtml

Privacy Statement for TranceAddict.com
TranceAddict™ has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our
firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices
for TranceAddict.com:
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information. We use this
information only for statistical purposes to find out where our visitors are
coming from and to resolve disputes. If you are known to be abusing system resources and/or disrupting
the overall functioning of the site then this information is used to block you
and depending on severity - also notify your Internet Service Provider.
Cookies
In order to prevent multiple pop-up advertisements from being displayed
to you while surfing on TranceAddict.com a cookie is set allowing us to know
that you have already seen a popup and won't have to deal with more of them
when moving throughout the site.
We use various outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. In-House Banner sales are hosted by us so as to protect your privacy, browsing habits and referring URLs.
Advertisers
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.
Personal Information
Use of this web site does not require any personal information or collection
any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally
contacted. Registration in the forums and/or the TranceAddict.com mailing list
only requires that you submit your e-mail address and country of residence.
These e-mail addresses are NOT publically accessible but keep in mind
if you post your e-mail address in the a message within the forums then it may
be picked up by a search engine (alternatively you can send a Private Message
(via the forums) to the user you wish to send your e-mail address to).
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. TranceAddict™ is not responsible for
the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Contests
Our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation
in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore
has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information
typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address),
and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be
used [shared with the contest [survey] sponsors] to notify the winners and award
prizes.
Tell-A-Friend
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our
site, we ask them for the friend?s name and email address. TranceAddict™ will
automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site.
TranceAddict™ stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time
email (to prevent duplication and spam abuse). The friend may contact TranceAddict™
at http://www.tranceaddict.com/contact.php
to request the removal of this information from our database.
Google Ads / Reporting
We use Google Analytics software to help give us insight as to who our visitors are - we also utilize Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. TranceAddict and third-party vendors,
including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad
services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.
Many sites on the net use this reporting tool - if you would like to opt-out please visit https://google.com/settings and follow the instructions.
Sharing Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose
personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief
that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding,
a court order or legal process served on our Web site.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this
privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so our
users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under
what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance
with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however,
we are going to use users? personally identifiable information in a manner different
from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users
will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different
manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site,
or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will
their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make
any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information
already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site
notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will
also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying
them of the changes in our privacy practices.
Link Theft
We do not condone direct link(s) to digital media and other large files on external web/ftp sites on the
TranceAddict.com forums. Please link
to the originating source and have respect for other webmasters and the time
they put in to maintain their pages. Alternatively, it is also not acceptable to post direct links to
files on our TranceAddict.com servers - please direct all links to www.tranceaddict.com
instead.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please
contact us at: http://www.tranceaddict.com/feedback.shtml
Last Modified: March 28th 2014
